[
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate loves a good cocktail?",
    "Option_A": "Jonathan",
    "Option_B": "Mia",
    "Option_C": "Mika",
    "Option_D": "Jenny",
    "Answer": "Mika",
    "": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate used to be allergic to pineapple?",
    "Option_A": "Jolyn",
    "Option_B": "Vee",
    "Option_C": "Irene",
    "Option_D": "Huijie",
    "Answer": "Vee",
    "": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate has 6 siblings?",
    "Option_A": "Amely",
    "Option_B": "Shambhavi",
    "Option_C": "Nadia",
    "Option_D": "Jennifer",
    "Answer": "Amely",
    "": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmates are married (not to each other but just married)?",
    "Option_A": "Irene and Devansh",
    "Option_B": "Inji and Bhakti",
    "Option_C": "Bhakti and Ishani",
    "Option_D": "Mika and Bee",
    "Answer": "Bhakti and Ishani",
    "": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmates play soccer?",
    "Option_A": "Amy and Jenny",
    "Option_B": "Devansh and Emma",
    "Option_C": "Hannah and Yuting",
    "Option_D": "Hannah and Emma",
    "Answer": "Hannah and Emma",
    "": "D"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate is a cute Korean girl?",
    "Option_A": "Yaxuan",
    "Option_B": "Inji",
    "Option_C": "Mia",
    "Option_D": "Jonathan",
    "Answer": "Mia",
    "": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate has major cooking skills?",
    "Option_A": "Bhakti",
    "Option_B": "Mika",
    "Option_C": "Opal",
    "Option_D": "Rice",
    "Answer": "Bhakti",
    "": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate was on an episode of iCarly?",
    "Option_A": "Hannah",
    "Option_B": "Rayana",
    "Option_C": "Hye Lynn",
    "Option_D": "Ziwei",
    "Answer": "Rayana",
    "": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate doesn't like any U.S. food?",
    "Option_A": "Jennifer",
    "Option_B": "Iris",
    "Option_C": "Ishani",
    "Option_D": "Inji",
    "Answer": "Inji",
    "": "D"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate loves the color black?",
    "Option_A": "Shambhavi",
    "Option_B": "Yaxuan",
    "Option_C": "Hye Lynn",
    "Option_D": "Rice",
    "Answer": "Hye Lynn",
    "": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate was born in Pennsylvania?",
    "Option_A": "Devansh",
    "Option_B": "Iris",
    "Option_C": "Rayana",
    "Option_D": "Irene",
    "Answer": "Iris",
    "": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate has two cats?",
    "Option_A": "Rice",
    "Option_B": "Opal",
    "Option_C": "Amely",
    "Option_D": "Ziwei",
    "Answer": "Rice",
    "": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate does not know how to read?",
    "Option_A": "Bee",
    "Option_B": "Vee",
    "Option_C": "Emma",
    "Option_D": "Jonathan",
    "Answer": "Jonathan",
    "": "D"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate is baby?",
    "Option_A": "Hye Lynn",
    "Option_B": "Jolyn",
    "Option_C": "Yaxuan",
    "Option_D": "Ziwei",
    "Answer": "Jolyn",
    "": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which classmate has been skydiving?",
    "Option_A": "Amy",
    "Option_B": "Nadia",
    "Option_C": "Huijie",
    "Option_D": "Bee",
    "Answer": "Amy",
    "": "A"
  }
]